(Bernadette:)What is it about trains
that you like so much?
(Sheldon:)What an interesting
question.
(Sheldon:)When I was a child,
life was confusing
(Sheldon:)and chaotic for me, and
trains represented order.
(Sheldon:)I could line them up,
categorize them, control them.
(Sheldon:)I guess you
could say that
(Sheldon:)they gave me a sense of calm
in a world that didn't.
(Bernadette:)That's lovely, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Well... other than when they're
chugging through your bowels,
(Sheldon:)these things are magic.
(Leonard:)I have to admit,
I've been worried about
(Leonard:)the military applications since
we started talking about this.
(Howard:)Me, too.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you
say something?
(Howard:)Same reason I don't
talk about ass cancer.
(Howard:)It's not a
pleasant topic.
(Raj:)You can't let this stop you.
(Raj:)Almost any scientific
advancement can be used
(Raj:)for destructive purposes.
(Amy:)It's true. Even Einstein's
theory of relativity
(Amy:)was later applied to the
development of nuclear weapons.
(Penny:)E equals MC squared.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
“E” is for energy,
“M” for mass,
and “C” for the speed of light.